A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1971-1980 FA401
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1973
  - United States, 1973/200
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1973/200.A
      - Association of American Medical Colleges (International Education) (Reel 59, Frame 711)
      - Association of American Medical Colleges (International Education Conference) (Reel 59, Frame 1012)
      - A-C (Reel 59, Frame 1022)
      - University of Missouri (Medical School) (Reel 59, Frame 1095)
      - University (I-W) (Reel 60, Frame 1)
      - Vanderbilt University (Medical School) (Reel 60, Frame 13)
      - Washington University (Medical School) (Reel 60, Frame 18)
      - D-W (Reel 60, Frame 21)
      - Yale University, Medical School (Berliner, Robert W.) (Reel 60, Frame 234)
    - United States - Nursing, 1973/200.C
      - D-M (Reel 60, Frame 239)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/200.D
      - Cornell University (Agriculture) (Reel 60, Frame 243)
    - United States - Fellowships, 1973/200.E
      - B-W (Reel 60, Frame 279)
    - United States - Declinations, 1973/200.F
      - N-O (Reel 60, Frame 414)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1973/200.R
      - United Association for Retarded Children (Reel 60, Frame 578)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, 1973/200.W
      - C-W (Reel 60, Frame 590)
  - Philippines, 1973/242
    - A-S (Reel 60, Frame 645)
    - University of the Philippines (A-R) (Reel 60, Frame 968)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, 1973/242.E
      - University of the Philippines (Reel 61, Frame 1)
  - Puerto Rico, 1973/243
    - I-W (Reel 61, Frame 17)
  - Samoa, 1973/245
    - Samoa (Environmental Quality Commission) (Reel 61, Frame 31)
  - Internship Program - Minority School Superintendents, 1973/260
    - Candidates (D-W) (Reel 61, Frame 164)
  - Internship Program - Minority Group Administrators of Government Funded Assistance Programs, 1973/262
    - Candidates (C-H) (Reel 61, Frame 246)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1973/272
    - Erickson, Pat (Reel 61, Frame 254)
    - F-T (Reel 61, Frame 285)
    - Unger, Robert L. (Reel 61, Frame 294)
  - South America and Latin America, 1973/300
    - I (Reel 61, Frame 331)
    - South America and Latin America - Medical Sciences, 1973/300.A
      - Pan American Federation of Medical Schools (Population) (Reel 61, Frame 781)
      - Pan American Federation of Medical Schools (Supplementary Material) (Reel 61, Frame 830)
    - South America and Latin America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/300.D
      - Corn Improvement (Reel 61, Frame 889)
  - Argentina, 1973/301
    - A-T (Reel 61, Frame 894)
  - Brazil, 1973/305
    - C-U (Reel 61, Frame 951)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/305.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 61, Frame 1033)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1973/305.E
      - Reis, Jose Osorio (Reel 61, Frame 1041)
    - Brazil - Schistosomiasis, 1973/305.W
      - University of Minas Gerais (Reel 61, Frame 1062)
  - Chile, 1973/309
    - B-U (Reel 62, Frame 1)
    - Santiago Demographic Center (Supplementary Material) (Reel 62, Frame 29)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/309.D
      - Catholic University (Agriculture) (Reel 62, Frame 360)
    - Chile - Fellowships, 1973/309.E
      - Yopo P., Boris (Reel 62, Frame 362)
  - Colombia, 1973/311
    - A-V (Reel 62, Frame 388)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1973/311.A
      - University of Antioquia (Medical School) (Reel 62, Frame 754)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/311.D
      - Colombian Agricultural Institute (B-G) (Reel 62, Frame 762)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, 1973/311.E
      - 311E (Reel 62, Frame 802)
      - A-Y (Reel 62, Frame 806)
  - Costa Rica, 1973/313
    - Q-U (Reel 62, Frame 1037)
  - Ecuador, 1973/317
    - A-T (Reel 63, Frame 1)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, 1973/317.E
      - Cabrera Ortiz, Julio Ernesto (Reel 63, Frame 47)
      - E-S (Reel 63, Frame 97)
  - Guatemala, 1973/319
    - G-U (Reel 63, Frame 171)
    - Guatemala - Medical Sciences, 1973/319.A
      - University of San Carlos (Medical School) (Reel 63, Frame 193)
    - Guatemala - Fellowships, 1973/319.E
      - Palencia Ortiz, Julio Anibal (Reel 63, Frame 196)
  - Haiti, 1973/320
    - D-U (Reel 63, Frame 230)
  - Honduras, 1973/321
    - Fick Ammann, Walter (Reel 63, Frame 240)
  - Mexico, 1973/323
    - A-S (Reel 63, Frame 254)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/323.D
      - Agricultural Education (Monterrey) (Reel 63, Frame 416)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, 1973/323.E
      - A-V (Reel 63, Frame 476)
  - Nicaragua, 1973/325
    - Central American University (Bendana R., Frank) (Reel 63, Frame 573)
  - Panama, 1973/327
    - A-R (Reel 63, Frame 586)
  - Paraguay, 1973/329
    - Paraguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/329.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 63, Frame 734)
  - Peru, 02.1973/331
    - A-V (Reel 63, Frame 744)
    - Peru - Fellowships, 1973/331.E
      - Palacios, Martin (Reel 63, Frame 760)
  - El Salvador, 1973/333
    - A-U (Reel 63, Frame 769)
  - Venezuela, 1973/339
    - C-T (Reel 63, Frame 805)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/339.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 63, Frame 817)
  - Great Britain, 1973/400
    - Commonwealth Development Corporation (Swynnerton, Roger J. M.) (Reel 63, Frame 911)
  - England, 1973/401
    - A-I (Reel 63, Frame 913)
    - University of Liverpool (Zaria Proposal) (Reel 64, Frame 1)
    - University (C-S) (Reel 64, Frame 43)
    - K-Y (Reel 64, Frame 191)
  - Ireland, 1973/403
    - H-U (Reel 64, Frame 438)
  - Scotland, 1973/405
    - Anderson, David F. (Reel 64, Frame 453)
  - Wales, 1973/407
    - University College of Wales (Green, D. A. G.) (Reel 64, Frame 457)
  - Malta, 1973/409
    - Euro-African Foundation (Reel 64, Frame 460)
  - Australia, 1973/410
    - A-U (Reel 64, Frame 473)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1973/420
    - Medical Research in the British Caribbean (Reel 64, Frame 542)
    - Caribbean Region and Central America - Medical Sciences, 1973/420.A
      - Caribbean Committee for Bilharzia Research (Reel 64, Frame 562)
  - Guyana, 1973/423
    - Allsopp, W. Herbert L. (Reel 64, Frame 593)
  - Canada, 1973/427
    - Perrault, Paul M. (Reel 64, Frame 597)
    - Royal Winnipeg Ballet (Scholarship Class) (Reel 64, Frame 653)
    - University of Guelph (I-V) (Reel 64, Frame 695)
    - B-Y (Reel 64, Frame 793)
  - Jamaica, 1973/437
    - P-U (Reel 64, Frame 1074)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, 1973/451
    - University of the West Indies (I-T) (Reel 65, Frame 1)
    - Trinidad and Tobago - Virus Studies, 1973/451.V
      - 451V (Reel 65, Frame 10)
  - Winward Islands, 1973/455
    - Windward Islands - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/455.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 65, Frame 12)
  - Sri Lanka, 1973/462
    - Sri Lanka - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/462.D
      - A-R (Reel 65, Frame 260)
  - Hong Kong, 1973/463
    - C-W (Reel 65, Frame 348)
  - India, 1973/464
    - A-U (Reel 65, Frame 352)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1973/464.A
      - A-N (Reel 65, Frame 475)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/464.D
      - India, Agriculture (N-S) (Reel 65, Frame 540)
  - Pakistan, 1973/465
    - Pakistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/465.D
      - A-R (Reel 65, Frame 545)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1973/466
    - K-U (Reel 65, Frame 559)
  - Malaysia, 1973/473
    - A-U (Reel 65, Frame 620)
    - Malaysia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/473.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 65, Frame 645)
  - Nepal, 1973/474
    - C-G (Reel 65, Frame 651)
  - Africa, 1973/475
    - Association (A-F) (Reel 65, Frame 659)
  - Kenya, 1973/476
    - A-U (Reel 65, Frame 866)
    - Kenya - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/476.D
      - University of Nairobi (A-G) (Reel 66, Frame 1)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, 1973/476.E
      - Mati, Jopheth Kimanzi Gideon (Reel 66, Frame 18)
  - East Africa Region, 1973/477
    - East African (C-V) (Reel 66, Frame 24)
  - Malawi, 1973/482
    - Krogstad, Donald J. (Reel 66, Frame 67)
  - Rhodesia, 1973/483
    - Private Game Reserve and Research Station (Reel 66, Frame 69)
  - South Africa Region, 1973/487
    - University of Botswana (H-S) (Reel 66, Frame 79)
  - Republic of South Africa, 1973/489
    - Mangope, Lucas (Reel 66, Frame 84)
  - Uganda, 1973/492
    - E-V (Reel 66, Frame 89)
    - Uganda - Fellowships, 1973/492.E
      - B-N (Reel 66, Frame 185)
    - Uganda - Social Sciences, 1973/492.S
      - Makerere University (Economics) (Reel 66, Frame 208)
  - Sudan, 1973/494
    - D-R (Reel 66, Frame 210)
  - West Africa Region, 1973/495
    - N-S (Reel 66, Frame 224)
    - West Africa Region - Fellowships, 1973/495.E
      - Dansala, Bambe R. (Reel 66, Frame 341)
  - Ghana, 1973/496
    - D-U (Reel 66, Frame 352)
  - Nigeria, 1973/497
    - University of Ibadan (A-V) (Reel 66, Frame 362)
    - A-U (Reel 66, Frame 515)
    - Nigeria - Medical Sciences, 1973/497.A
      - M-U (Reel 66, Frame 799)
    - Nigeria - Nursing, 1973/497.C
      - University of Ibadan (Reel 66, Frame 817)
    - Nigeria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/497.D
      - A-U (Reel 66, Frame 819)
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, 1973/497.E
      - Ogionwo, William W. (Reel 66, Frame 866)
      - A-O (Reel 66, Frame 934)
  - Nigeria - Declinations Outside Program, 1973/497.FO
    - Anya, Chinedum Oji (Reel 66, Frame 1015)
  - Sierra Leone, 1973/499
    - F-U (Reel 66, Frame 1019)
  - France, 1973/500
    - Roquette Laboratory (Algae Culturing System) (Reel 66, Frame 1043)
    - B-T (Reel 67, Frame 1)
    - France - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/500.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 67, Frame 319)
  - Algeria, 1973/501
    - Yaker, Abdenour (Reel 67, Frame 346)
    - Algeria - Fellowships, 1973/501.E
      - Hachemi, Lounes (Reel 67, Frame 360)
  - Vietnam, 1973/509
    - N-T (Reel 67, Frame 371)
  - Tunisia, 1973/539
    - Oceanographic Institution (Reel 67, Frame 388)
  - Asia and Far East Asia, 1973/600
    - Asian Association of Development Research and Training Institutes (Reel 67, Frame 391)
    - Asia and Far East Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/600.D
      - G-R (Reel 67, Frame 462)
  - People's Republic of China, 1973/601
    - C (Reel 67, Frame 597)
  - Taiwan, 1973/605
    - Asian Vegetable Research and Development Center (Reel 67, Frame 610)
    - Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction (Multiple Cropping) (Reel 68, Frame 1)
    - J-T (Reel 68, Frame 295)
    - Taiwan - Fellowships, 1973/605.E
      - Lee, Ten Hin (Reel 68, Frame 302)
    - Taiwan - Schistosomiasis, 1973/605.W
      - Kwangtung Institute (Jen, Yen Jui) (Reel 68, Frame 304)
  - Japan, 1973/609
    - H-T (Reel 68, Frame 317)
  - Korea, 1973/613
    - Korea - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/613.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 68, Frame 364)
  - Thailand, 1973/617
    - A-U (Reel 68, Frame 366)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/617.D
      - A-K (Reel 68, Frame 546)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1973/617.E
      - 617E (Reel 68, Frame 610)
      - A-P (Reel 68, Frame 624)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1973/617.S
      - University of Thammasat (Economics) (Reel 68, Frame 645)
  - Holland, 1973/650
    - D-W (Reel 68, Frame 867)
  - Indonesia, 1973/652
    - Indonesian Society of Agricultural Economics (Conference) (Reel 68, Frame 937)
    - A-W (Reel 68, Frame 996)
    - Indonesia - Medical Sciences, 1973/652.A
      - University of Indonesia (Public Health Faculty) (Reel 69, Frame 1)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1973/652.E
      - 652E (Reel 69, Frame 75)
      - A-W (Reel 69, Frame 80)
  - Ethiopia, 1973/701
    - H-N (Reel 69, Frame 150)
    - Ethiopia - Medical Sciences, 1973/701.A
      - Haile Selassie I University (Reel 69, Frame 158)
    - Ethiopia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/701.D
      - A-G (Reel 69, Frame 171)
    - Ethiopia - Fellowships, 1973/701.E
      - Bekele, Girma (Reel 69, Frame 258)
  - Afghanistan, 1973/703
    - Fedai, Zia Mohamad (Reel 69, Frame 274)
  - Belgium, 1973/707
    - D-W (Reel 69, Frame 277)
  - Zaire, 1973/709
    - D-Z (Reel 69, Frame 331)
    - Zaire - Medical Sciences, 1973/709.A
      - National University of Zaire (Health Services) (Reel 69, Frame 469)
    - Zaire - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/709.D
      - A-M (Reel 69, Frame 488)
    - Zaire - Fellowships, 1973/709.E
      - L-M (Reel 69, Frame 539)
  - Germany, 1973/717
    - B-W (Reel 69, Frame 556)
  - Tanzania, 1973/723
    - H-U (Reel 69, Frame 707)
    - Tanzania - Fellowships, 1973/723.E
      - K-M (Reel 69, Frame 750)
  - Zambia, 1973/724
    - University of Zambia (Goma) (Reel 69, Frame 762)
  - Cameroon, 1973/735
    - Otabela, Prothais (Reel 69, Frame 765)
  - Togo, 1973/745
    - University of Benin (Reel 69, Frame 772)
  - Greece, 1973/749
    - D-Z (Reel 69, Frame 805)
  - Italy, 1973/751
    - A-U (Reel 69, Frame 946)
  - Libya, 1973/758
    - Kamal, Ahmed M. (Reel 69, Frame 974)
  - Liberia, 1973/759
    - L-U (Reel 69, Frame 982)
  - Norway, 1973/767
    - A-F (Reel 69, Frame 1015)
  - Iran, 1973/771
    - M-W (Reel 69, Frame 1020)
  - Portugal, 1973/773
    - B-S (Reel 69, Frame 1058)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR), 1973/785
    - Gromeka, Vasily I. (Reel 69, Frame 1063)
  - Finland, 1973/787
    - R-V (Reel 69, Frame 1067)
  - Poland, 1973/789
    - L-U (Reel 69, Frame 1100)
  - Spain, 1973/795
    - General Mediterranean Foundation (Reel 69, Frame 1123)
    - Spain - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/795.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 69, Frame 1131)
  - Sweden, 1973/800
    - B-U (Reel 70, Frame 1)
  - Switzerland, 1973/803
    - A-S (Reel 70, Frame 123)
  - Turkey, 1973/805
    - A-U (Reel 70, Frame 175)
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1973/805.D
      - A-C (Reel 70, Frame 333)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, 1973/805.E
      - B-Y (Reel 70, Frame 375)
  - United Arab Republic, 1973/812
    - A-K (Reel 70, Frame 398)
  - Jordan, 1973/816
    - Jayyusi, Salma Khadra (Reel 70, Frame 450)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1973/817
    - Arid Lands Research Center (Reel 70, Frame 453)
  - Israel, 1973/825
    - Hebrew University (Food Legumes) (Reel 70, Frame 456)
    - Israel Exploration Society (Jerusalem Excavations) (Reel 70, Frame 728)
    - B-Z (Reel 70, Frame 734)
  - Lebanon, 1973/833
    - Arid Lands Agricultural Development (F-H) (Reel 70, Frame 842)
    - A-B (Reel 70, Frame 1163)
  - Members and Meetings, 1973/903
    - B-W (Reel 70, Frame 1187)
- General Correspondence, 1974
  - International, 1974; 1974/100
    - Aitken, Thomas H. G., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Allen, Jane, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 21)
    - Almy, Susan W., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 33)
    - Anderson, Charles R., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 56)
    - Andrews, Lowry, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 60)
    - Arbab, Farzam, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 64)
    - Arey, June Batten, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 74)
    - Baldwin, William, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 82)
    - Barker, Randolph, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 84)
    - Barnes, Allan C., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 90)
    - Barnish, Guy, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 260)
    - Bartholomew, Richard K., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 263)
    - Bertrand, Trent, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 265)
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 268)
    - Bradfield, Richard, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 288)
    - Bronte, D. Lydia, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 313)
    - Buckley, Sonia, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 316)
    - Byrnes, Francis C., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 323)
    - Callaghy, Thomas, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 334)
    - Casals, Jordi, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 336)
    - Chandler, Robert F., Jr., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 353)
    - Christie, John D., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 369)
    - Cole, Patricia Lou, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 386)
    - Coleman, James S., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 416)
    - Colton, Joel, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 422)
    - Connell, Elizabeth, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 496)
    - Cook, Joseph A., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 498)
    - Court, David, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 545)
    - Cummings, Ralph W., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 549)
    - Dalton, Peter, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 777)
    - Daunys, Alexander, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 800)
    - Davidson, Ralph K., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 803)
    - Davis, L. Harlan, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 805)
    - Delehanty, George E., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 838)
    - Dinning, James S., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 841)
    - Douglas, Johnson E., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 885)
    - Downs, Wilbur G., 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 993)
    - Durana, Ines, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 998)
    - Eddy, Junius, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 1046)
    - Eltherington, Lorne, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 1050)
    - Finfrock, Dwight, 1974 (Reel 1, Frame 1079)
    - Fischelis, Robert, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
    - Freeman, Wayne H., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 6)
    - Gilpatric, Chadbourne, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 64)
    - Golden, William G., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 67)
    - Gould, David J., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 111)
    - Grant, Jerry, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 122)
    - Grant, Ulysses J., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 124)
    - Gray, Clarence C. III, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 148)
    - Gregg, Lucien A., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 170)
    - Haag, Wayne, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 202)
    - Harrar, J. George, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 208)
    - Harris, P., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 271)
    - Harwood, Roland E., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 273)
    - Hayes, Guy S., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 295)
    - Helfrich, Philip, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 363)
    - Hildebrand, Peter E., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 371)
    - Holland, Robert C., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 374)
    - House, Leland R., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 387)
    - Huggins, Russell, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 427)
    - Ingles, Thelma, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 439)
    - Jackson, Elmore, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 487)
    - Jennings, Peter R., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 516)
    - Jenson, James, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 543)
    - Johnson, Lloyd, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 557)
    - Johnston, James E., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 561)
    - Jordan, Peter, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 586)
    - Katz, Stephen M., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 614)
    - Kemp, Graham E., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 625)
    - Kirschner, L., 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 630)
    - Klein, Howard, 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 632)
    - Knowles, John H. (January), 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 702)
    - Knowles, John H. (February), 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 824)
    - Knowles, John H. (March), 1974 (Reel 2, Frame 990)
    - Knowles, John H. (April), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Knowles, John H. (May), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 205)
    - Knowles, John H. (June), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 342)
    - Knowles, John H. (July), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 540)
    - Knowles, John H. (August), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 636)
    - Knowles, John H. (September), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 710)
    - Knowles, John H. (October), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 770)
    - Knowles, John H. (November), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 868)
    - Knowles, John H. (December), 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 916)
    - Kritz, Mary M., 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 991)
    - Kuperman, Albert S., 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 995)
    - Laird, Reggie J., 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 1041)
    - Lathem, Willoughby, 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 1084)
    - Lee, Vernon H., 1974 (Reel 3, Frame 1118)
    - Long, E. Croft, 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - MacLellan, Neil B., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 99)
    - Maier, John, 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 113)
    - Mann, Charles K., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 157)
    - McCleary, Willima, 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 179)
    - McClung, A. Colin, 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 183)
    - McKelvey, John J., Jr., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 209)
    - Miller, Leonard, 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 345)
    - Moomaw, James C., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 348)
    - Moore, Charles L., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 394)
    - Morris, O. Frank, 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 407)
    - Moseman, Albert H., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 421)
    - Neumann, Ellsworth T., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 477)
    - Newburgh, R. W., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 489)
    - Nickel, John L., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 509)
    - Niederhauser, John S., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 552)
    - Northrup, Robert S., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 555)
    - Novak, Michael (January-April), 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 608)
    - Novak, Michael (May-August), 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 726)
    - Novak, Michael (September-December), 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 864)
    - Nyberg, Albert J., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 961)
    - Olson, James A., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 964)
    - Olson, William C., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 1029)
    - Oshima, Harry T., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 1054)
    - Osler, Robert D., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 1062)
    - Owens, Patrick N., 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 1064)
    - Parker, Dorothy, 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 1117)
    - Parson, William, 1974 (Reel 4, Frame 1147)
    - Perry, Jesse P., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
    - Pino, John A., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 6)
    - Plank, Stephen J., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 186)
    - Porter, Wayne, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 225)
    - Prentice, Michael A., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 282)
    - Pritchard, W. R., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 312)
    - Rachie, Kenneth O., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 330)
    - Raun, Ned S., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 335)
    - Reitz, J. Wayne, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 378)
    - Renfro, Bobby L., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 381)
    - Richardson, Ralph W., Jr., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 469)
    - Roberts, Lewis M., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 544)
    - Rohde, Jon E., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 569)
    - Romney, Henry, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 635)
    - Ross, Vernon, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 640)
    - Sadun, Elvio H., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 642)
    - Sawyer, William D., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 658)
    - Sayer, Ken D., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 661)
    - Schad, Marjorie, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 664)
    - Schoepf, Brooke, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 666)
    - Scott, Virgil C., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 668)
    - Shope, Robert E., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 757)
    - Smeltzer, Dale G., 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 784)
    - Speir, Robert, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 805)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (Wray, Joe D.), 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 807)
    - Staff Members Occasional Papers (D-S), 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 976)
    - Stamm, Esther, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 1103)
    - Starnes, Ordway, 1974 (Reel 5, Frame 1109)
    - Stephenson, Marvin, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - Stifel, Laurence D., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 14)
    - Stremlau, John J., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 29)
    - Sturrock, Robert F., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 34)
    - Tillman, Allen D., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 37)
    - Todaro, Michael P., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 64)
    - Toenniessen, Gary H., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 71)
    - Traywick, Jack Dee, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 94)
    - Turner, Thomas E., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 101)
    - Unrau, Gladwin O., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 103)
    - Upatham, Edward S., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 124)
    - Velazquez Palau, Gabriel, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 149)
    - Warren, Kenneth S., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 189)
    - Watt, Earl E., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 333)
    - Waugh, Robert K., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 359)
    - Weidemann, Wesley C., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 380)
    - Weir, John M., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 384)
    - Wellhausen, Edwin J., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 388)
    - Welsch, Delane E., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 467)
    - Wernimont, Kenneth, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 511)
    - White, Colin, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 525)
    - Williams, Bruce E., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 534)
    - Winikoff, Beverly, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 536)
    - Wolling, Frank, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 538)
    - Wood, Peter H., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 540)
    - Wortman, L. Sterling, 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 602)
    - Wray, Joe D., 1974 (Reel 6, Frame 1121)
    - Wright, Christopher, 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Young, M. Crawford, 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 37)
    - Young, William R., 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 40)
  - International Organizations, 1974; 1974/103
    - China Medical Board of New York, Inc., 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 72)
    - International (A-F), 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 120)
    - International (I-W), 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 396)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation (Supplementary Material), 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 618)
    - Trilateral Commission, 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 640)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (Fear, Grant), 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 848)
    - United Nations, Food and Agriculture Organization (C-K), 1974 (Reel 7, Frame 952)